[Music]
where we feel kebina regular income
we need to cut down on our needs hamik
simple couple
all we want is a stress-free retirement
life that's why we need a plan that will
help us manage our daily expenses while
we make the most of our retirement years
by fulfilling our dreams and goals
morning newspapers
presenting a retirement plan specially
designed for your needs
icici pro guaranteed pension plan flexi
this plan is designed for people between
the age of 45 to 60 years and looking to
save for their retirement
the plan lets you invest small amounts
of money for a period of 15 years and
ensures a guaranteed income for life
so restart your life post retirement on
your own terms with icici pro guaranteed
pension plan flexi
the icic approved guaranteed pension
plan flexi also offers multiple benefits
regular income with regular savings
choice of 7 annuity options as per your
needs
unique options like accelerated health
boosters and booster payouts that
provide a periodic lump sum payout to
take care of your healthcare and
lifestyle needs
one percent additional annuity for
existing icici prudential life insurance
customers
save the date feature to receive your
income on the date of your choice
top-up facility to increase your income
by paying an additional premium
loan facility to get access to money
when you need it
[Music]
so
you